

Haris Ratno Pambudi, ST

Experienced with 5 years of work experience at PT Bank Rakyat Indonesia, Tbk. Possessing knowledge and skills in operating hardware and software, as well as good analytical ability in solving technical problems. Willing to contribute more to the company.





Purwakarta, Indonesia harisratnopambudi@gmail.com 087784477751



Skill

Tech Stack











JavaScript



Developer Tools



Visual Studio



GitHub



Visual Studio Code



Work Experience



Universal Banker Non Financial • PT Bank Rakyat Indonesia (persero) Tbk

September 2017 - December 2020

Served as a Frontliner in the position of Customer Service for 3 (three) years.



Universal Banker Financial • PT Bank Rakyat Indonesia (persero) Tbk

January 2021 - August 2022

Served as a Frontliner in the position of Teller for 2 (two) years.

Pendidikan



2011 - 2015

Sekolah Tinggi Teknologi Wastukancana Purwakarta

Bachelor's Degree in Informatics Engineering

GPA 3.24 / 4.00

Thesis: Pembuatan Game Edukasi "Yuk Mengenal Hewan" Sebagai Pembelajaran Berbagai Macam Suara Hewan Untuk Anak Usia Dini Berbasis Android".

Certification

- BSDP Reskilling Pekerja BRI Campus Surabaya 2022
- The Hour of Code www.code.org